# **Aaron An**

#### SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### **Profile**

Interested in all aspects of computer science, especially in development, engineering, data analytics and mobile applications. Strong background in computer science. Hold more than 5 years of coding experience and designing software applications. Capable of combining computer science skills and business knowledge to resolve difficult problems.

### **Experiences**

Software Engineer (Intern)

Aug 2020 – Dec 2020

## QMSC LLC, Remote

- Created PHP enhancements and new functionalities for backend systems.
- Corrected errors and various bugs in JS/JQuery and PHP.
- Used SQL to make new databases or to edit existing databases.
- Supported senior engineers and project managers plan for future sprints.
- Proposed new functionalities and user-focused upgrades that would be beneficials for current/future users.

Software Engineer (Intern)

Jan 2020 - Apr 2020

#### StockX, Detroit, MI

- Developed PHP endpoints to assist with system self-healing capabilities.
- Worked with senior developers to create Python and PHP controllers that monitors the accuracy of the system.
- Transposed existing Python features to native PHP backend.
- Created unit tests in PHP to verify system functionalities and behaviors.
- Deployed monolith/database and ensured proper system behaviors.

#### **Extracurricular Activities**

Windsor Tech Club Member

Jan 2016 – Aug 2019

University of Windsor, Windsor, ON, Canada

- Helped local businesses update websites with HTML, CSS, and JS.
- Designed and developed traffic monitoring features for client websites.
- Helped building, maintaining and improving projects or products.

## **Projects and Development Experiences**

- Calibrated with other students and developed a bus navigation system for a contest hosted by the city of Detroit, placed third overall. Built with Java and Python.
- Designed and developed an Android streaming application that allows the users to stream events or watch available streams. Designed with Google APIs and FireBase API.
- Worked with monolithic structures. Built PHP controllers to determine the accuracy of data stored in the database.

### **Contact Information**



(248) 635-8456



aaronan1996@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/aaron-m-an sagittariux.github.io



Troy, Michigan

## **Technology Stack**













## **Tools Stack**







## **Education**

#### **University of Windsor**

Computer Science & Business Admin. Class of 2019

- Graduated with distinction

